NYU Tamiment Library Collection of National Coat and Suit Recovery Board Documents (copy 2) on Microfilm 6168 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
NYU Tamiment Library Collection of National Coat and Suit Recovery Board Documents (copy 2) on Microfilm
1933-1972
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Coat and Suit Recovery Board
6168 mf
2.11 cubic feet
19 microfilm reels
Reports, minutes, pamphlets, correspondence, publiations, proceedings, records, microflm.
16391343
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 14, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, July 14, 2015
Biographical / Historical
The Coat and Suit Industry National Recovery Board came about for the purpose of assuring that garments were made in accordance with the Fair Labor Standards. The 'union label' was placed on garments that were made by workers who were not working excessive hours and who were being paid fair hourly wages.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6167 mf: NYU Tamiment Library Collection of National Coat and Suit Recovery Board Documents on Microfilm
National Coat and Suit Recovery Board
16391343
- Chicago offices: S.J. Kantor records. (Reel 1)
- Chicago office: Professional correspondence, 1934-1935; Account reports, 1934-1935. (Reel 1A)
- Chicago office: Professional correspondence, 1934-1935; Account reports, 1934-1935. Duplicate. (Reel 1B)
- Chicago offices: S.J. Kantor records; Coat and Suit Authority: Nathan Wolf correspondence, Oct. 1934. (Reel 2)
- Coat and Suit Authority: Nathan Wolf correspondence, 1934; Coat and Suit Authority: St. Louis office correspondence, 1934. (Reel 3)
- Coat and Suit Authority: St. Louis office correspondence, 1934; National Recovery Board: Semi-annual meeting proceedings, August 1937. (Reel 4)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, 1952-1954 (Reel 6)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, Jnauary, 1954 (Reel 7)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: National Executive Board, 1960 (Reel 8)
- Correspondence (Reel 9)
- ILGWU Census Report, 1964 (Reel 10)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Annual Meeting, 1964 (Reel 11)
- Minutes of Meeting of the Sub-Committee on Trafficing, 1970 (Reel 12)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: National Executive Board: 5th semiannual meeting, January 1938; ILGWU: Pacific Coast Regional Board: Amendments to Constitution, June 1941. (Reel 13)
- National Coat and Suit Recovery Board: Activities and Operations, November 1940 - March 1941. (Reel 14)
- Coat and Suit Authority: Agreement with Office and Professional Employees Union, 1970; Hearings of Ad Fund violations, June 1961. (Reel 15)
- Tamiment Library (Reel 16)
- Tamiment Library (Reel 17)
- National Retailers monthly bulletin (Reel 18)